#### Contact

ntwarijoseph2050@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ngabonzizantwali-joseph-△#-544a2618b (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

React.js JavaScript Node.js

### Certifications

AWS Certified Solutions Architect – Associate

Cyber Security Bootcamp

# Ngabonziza Ntwali Joseph #



Kigali City, Rwanda

## Summary

"Live the Life of Your Dreams

When you start living the life of your dreams, there will always be obstacles, doubters, mistakes and setbacks along the way. But with hard work, perseverance and self-belief there is no limit to what you can achieve."

Roy T. Bennett, The Light in the Heart
Hello! My name is Ngabonziza Joseph with experience in cloud computing, Networking and WordPress. I have experience in collaborating with cross-functional teams in building sustainable products that meets customer specifications.

- .I believe that empathy is a great foundation on which any successful product is built.
- . I also get to implement my analytical, creative, communication and team working skills to develop products while working with stakeholders and other team members from other disciplines.
- .Skills: Networking, AWS Solutions Architect, Front End Development(React Js), WordPress (WOO Commerce, Elementor and Using themes and other plugins), Figma, Trello, UI/UX Design.

I'm open to work remotely, on-site or hybrid roles

# Experience

Andela Andela Intern November 2022 - Present (3 months) Kigali City, Rwanda

Nova Services Ltd. Networking Trainer

#### April 2022 - December 2022 (9 months)

Kigali, Kigali City, Rwanda

Performing Routing and switching concepts, Interpreting Windows server and implement some Hardware and software maintenances.

Azubi Africa

Cloud Solutions Architect (AWS)

April 2022 - November 2022 (8 months)

Kigali, Kigali City, Rwanda

2x Certificates of Amazon Web Services(AWS) both ( Cloud practitioner & Solutions Architecture) in duration of 12 weeks.

Through the whole program we used alot of amazing services like Amazon S3, API Gateway, Deploying Amazon EC2, Hosting Static website on S3.

kLab.rw

Front End/Wordpress Developer

April 2022 - October 2022 (7 months)

Kigali City, Rwanda

Designing Data center live project that includes hosting options, Domain purchasing, Networking services and Maintenance services.

## Education

University of Rwanda

Bachelor's degree, Business Information Technology · (April 2021)